This is the menu again after the after. Okay, so I think you need to choose the tutorial as well. Yeah
And maybe I mean just I mean I could also use brothers what the hell
Well, yeah, I don't see why you wouldn't be able to
Wait, can you use hentai?
Bro
We can't you do it. Does it let you do it?
Why would it let me do it?
Try it
Oh my god it did
Why did it work? Why did it work?
Let's I go back
Go back to what you talk about you talk about anything you talk about anything
I did go back. Okay, nevermind fault. It didn't cancel. Thank God
You still use hentai?
Thank you don't scam me like that bro
There's the most important thing right now
I'm everything my guy right now
You're making a character
I made mine already. Dude looks fucking ugly as hell. I
believe it
They're based off you then you're definitely I mean you can't change the default guys look make yourself a woman
No, I should look you and maybe we can have sex in the camper bin
He's a bit
I want to see what the sex scene is like in the case of a bit suss sussie baka
Also, I'm recording you know, I'm kitchen all of this sustenance right now
Yeah
Shell silver steamed
I don't even know who that is
The first celebrity name that came to my mind. I don't even know who that is
I
Have you gasping for air like what's his name? I love you for time
Yeah
I'm telling you that
No
Like what's his name
Don't know hint. Yeah, you mean it said dude who plays
Minecraft dream one of their names. I
Don't know why the fuck would I know their names? You think I'm a fucking 12 year old
Why the fuck would I know the name of one of dreams friends
Why do you know the names of one of dreams friends?
That's a dream
What the fuck I just put it on before I go to bed sometimes
Also, I'm in I'm driving around right now, but they're talking so you quite also turned it up
Am I done a tutorial? Oh, I am done a tutorial
Are you doing the tutorial?
I'm driving around
I open your menu click multiplayer into this a show multiplayer code
You need to comfort the intro for before I be able to hear the girl
Hey, you can't say that
Why not I'm black. Oh, yeah, I forgot
Nox, I don't want that disability labeled on me now
Okay
I'm getting canceled. That's where
Just
I'm invincible
That guy from the tv shows dad plowed him through a tree
So dad plowed in through a tree
Bro, what is up for it save as a fire as a campfire like who saved yourself at a campfire like
I'm just gonna go to the campfire and strike it up
But just come back here every time I need to go somewhere else
Dark souls
Yeah, I'm saying why you're like, why is that a thing just because dark souls invented it and just everyone just copy dark
Okay, I can did you try to jump off the cliff? Yeah, there was a wall there. Yeah
Oh
If I want to kill myself, I should be allowed to do it
Right, I'm literally
Who's who knows?
I'm telling you
No, I'm so close to say please
You need a first letter of his name. Please say please
Okay, please tell me the first letter of his name. Okay boy. It's just it's jean
George Floyd
Anyway, as I'm plowing you in our RV because you picked a woman. I'm gonna make you gasp for air like George Floyd
Type shit
Type shit you may just have a woman right? Nope
Okay
Could you imagine?
It's like you're married to your wife like 18 years and one day you're like, yeah, I decided that I didn't advise a woman. You're gay now
Crafts one rent and the open for all the two people watching this on youtube
Yo, yo, yo, what are you doing? You're just giving me work to edit and then quit it
I know I am
Open the mirror
Except for this part based amazing
But try to fire a lookout
Come on, I know what I'm doing. I got a lot
Where's the dirt road at?
Is there a
I'm
Am I gonna make the rent and I don't know where to go
To the back of the van
You find the metal behind your van and then you go to the back of the van just like rose to parks went to the back of the bus
Wait, where did you find the metal that? All right here
You just crafted in the back of your van. Why is the pick up so slow?
I don't know, but I thought of something the other day, right? Yeah sure you did
I thought of something
I didn't see it on instagram. I swear I thought of this
I don't believe you women be lying so much. They probably just asked Rosa parks to just move over
I saw you saw it on instagram. I know you guys are talking about instagram
I thought about this the other day. No, how's her husband also has a car?
I also thought about this the other day. Did you know Japan
Come here Judas
You know what's hilarious? No, I don't know
Shit on like an article like three or four years ago that Japan was starting to implement that like thing into their crosswalks
And all of a sudden everyone instagram was like, hey guys, you know this I'm like, oh, I thought everyone knew this already
knew what
That Japan was putting like pressure plates underneath some of their sidewalks to generate energy because so many people walked down in jibulia
Oh
Because that was like a pretty big talking point four years ago when they were first implementing it like I
My dad knew about that and my dad doesn't like know shit about anywhere outside of america and he knew that
It was a pretty big talking point for a while. I could go in the fire. I'm going to fire
All of a sudden, why would you walk over? Hey dude, this device
Oh, I'm supposed to leave the van to start walking down the path. Why don't you ah?
That's why I need to scratch the wrench. I don't know how to have anything to do walking down the path
Look at you craft the wrench. You can open the vent that opened the
Jerdum. I'm not paying attention. I'm just playing the game
Yeah, I wasn't thinking such an either and I thought you craft the wrench. You can open the fence and drive your car out
Oh, you're supposed to have the car out walking and go back and go
What would you want?
You can do multiplayer. Okay
It's a couple days
I'm doing tell you to hurry up and I'm doing taking the longest
Yeah, also I already told you name in the game when you told me to hurry up
Yeah, I told you before that you need to hurry up
Wigga
I don't say the n word. I say wig. That's how
I would never say the n word
Bro, how did you crash there was nothing in front of you
Brother, why are you blaming the character? Like you're not the one driving because he's a woman
So you did make yourself a woman. I did
Yeah, I'm not getting anymore. He's still gay
I literally named instagram gay
Therefore he's gay
You're like boys
No, shut up. You're like boys. You know it
Oh my goodness, please shut up
What should I make your name? That's not as funny
Nothing you do is as funny
Bon, blood, blood
for you wigga
Chick, oh, that's too many
Good
Okay, I'll do 47 bomb, but bro the club for you wigga
There you go
No one from school his name is uh, aloha Akbar bomber man
Night night join
You're not gonna believe it
What that looks nothing like, can't I?
I know
It was supposed to be hand-tied. That's what I think but I think the game would just stay to the bad work there and
Give me this random ass code
No, that's your that's the joint that's gonna be different every time it's the join code
So yeah, then your license plate is hand-tied
I didn't go check. You fucking idiot. Oh, it is. Oh my god. Actually
Bro, you gonna join my guy
I gotta remake my custom character. Oh my goodness, I'm gonna burn myself into fire see what happens
I'm gonna kill myself and see what happens
Fine dig me. I won't customize the colors because I took too long last time
I fainted
I'll say absolutely nothing happened. I know I have low health though
Why'd you make her black now? I don't want to fuck the shit out of you. That's good
Come here. Come here white boy. You got money on you white boys. Come here
You like this. Yeah, you like this two tang boy. Oh, no way for me
All right, that's fine. I'm gonna shout it now. Thank god
That's a field of have your car stolen and that's how you make your mind when you walk girls
You should be able to see that after you get in the car that's a driving pass
Bro, how do I?
You can't even get in. Is it one person? What's going on?
Yeah
You can drive
But we got to do we should
Where all right, let's just go
Yeah, what are we supposed to do? Is there a gas in this? Do we have to get gas?
Uh, probably
Brother I
Got it's a fucking car. Yep. Shit
We should do what the objectives say actually
Uh craft building ham. I use ginger to restore help using. I'm gonna find ginger. Hey, okay
Can we start the blue the blue bushes?
We can
Stop the cars. I can get out. Okay
You get
Too tired to sprint. Okay. I can get the very bushes
Yeah
Well, there's wood too tired to sprint. It took you so long to get past the tutorial. It became night time
Wow, and now we can't run because the night time
One different there's entering the woods
I'm gonna get attacked by a skinwalker. There's a bunch of fireflies. Oh, yeah, where are you? I dare you wear
What is that?
No kidding. I'm eating
Yeah, all right. I'm gonna back to the car before we get lost
You can see the car marked on the compass in the top of your screen
I see it Nate. It's so smart
There's a beacon
Birds got it
We're tired, Maurice. I cannot find the car
There is not like there's a big beacon telling where it is
Really?
I'm not running over. I'm not running over
Amorice maybe don't try killing a king now. Amorice. Amorice. Amorice
I dodged it Maurice. I'm a bad boy
Trying to get in the kilter please
I'm going to skin your balls
You do that middle mouse button
Let's not work in
Well Martin did I ping?
Look at the distance. Oh, look get out. Get out
You just look just look past look look at the mountain
Look, I'm picking the mountain too
Over there. I'm over here Nate
Why are we allowed to ping that far away?
Over here dog get in
Bro, they either means we're allowed to walk up there or that's just a crazy thing distance
They haven't fixed it. Oh, no. I see why we need to make a hammer now
Hammer
Yeah
You're going to chop down the trees with the hammer. I mean you can try you're not going to get far though
I think that we needed to make oh my god
Nate, why are you not doing this?
I think you know what I think you know, I don't care what you think I just made a hammer baby
I want to be able to sprint. That's what I think
Okay
I think I want to be allowed this sprint
You're gonna oh we can't close it
Get into bed
Shit
All right, that morning breath hose kicking dog
That morning what?
Breath
I'm morning breath. Yeah, I definitely morning breath and not the other kind of morning thing
That a guy would have
Yeah, I wonder what that guy would have I'm not a guy. I wouldn't know especially not for a black chick
All right building the RV because I already did this because I thought it was part of the tutorial
Building RV. Yeah, press B
Fuck you mean building the RV
Where am I building our foot a fold into I guess
No
Oh boo at least one car
Stupid
Where you gonna put the counter because I you fuck
Hey, you wanted me to build so you're gonna quit your comfort
Why would it not be decided better you could be a phone under or something dumb dumb
Because I don't roll off
I had a I used to have a thing beside my bed. I don't know the heck because it broke but I want another one
I would yeah
No, because first off wait, can I go through you?
Is there a hit though? There's no hit ticket. Okay. I thought there was hit detection because I have because we have to be on each side of the bed
I had to scoot over because it wasn't working
Okay
I thought that I didn't know we could go through each other. Also, you are super short
Is that just me like I have to look down to see your character
No, I'm looking at your big guy say right now. What am I looking for you?
No
You know those memes where it's like high angle pictures look forward
I
Look like one xbox 360 character, bro. Oh, you're right. Oh, you're right. We do
Are we gonna build the thing?
We need materials, dude
All right, let's go back to where there isn't a cross like a a tree trunk in the way
I look absolutely stunning, but you know what he's just racist lads. Don't worry about him
First off black women are disgusting. Jesus Christ. Where can I even post this?
YouTube stuff YouTube. I'm a minor. No, you're not going to need to
Wow
This session might be a gta one time
For legal purposes that was a joke
I'm from that part in doesn't for not a day now
No
Blueberries
I'm god-bung stuff. Is that ginger fiber and everwood
No, I'm making why making sounds for boy
The character making sound
Mason
You're hungry. How do I get food? I'm hungry. I put the blueberries in the car
And how do we get actors to it because I'm right here right here versus storage
I still definitely said that
goofy
Then some
Unsumption and I could some some fiber now
I'm turning the fiber into tickets for some reason
It's so flat
What you're flat, but I forgot your white so I'm a man
I shouldn't have a
You've seen gates started to gates
That's about a good thing
Gates is fucking gay
What is it looking so rabbit?
I kill it
But
You hitting the road
I'm trying to get my wood
I'm driving over there
Oh, they're doing over there. It's not putting no more way. Is it pinging?
I saw a bridge
Wanna go over to the bridge?
You drive
Wait, can you drive on to the back?
Oh, no, it just puts me
You got the wrong way that whoever came from
Why is it in reverse then
Look at this how we came from
It's going to be too far to the wood
Our car is not built for this
The car is not built for this
It'll be fine. I'm figuring out the glitter already
Just go just play this
You're playing this like it's GTA
You're hitting a log
Yeah, no, I'm trying to go around it
The collision for the vehicle is kind of weird
Hey, I think our car is dying
Is that the hp bar for the car or is that the power energy bar?
Stop. What is that? What's that? What is that? What is this?
What technology
Yes from the olden times. Yes, technology
Oh, act. Well, we need to take it. You need to take it to buy the X
Get out of the fucking computer
I mean, that's how both of us get the X to it
Yes, there we go. Yes. Uh, compute. Oh, I wanted to get the pick X to it
Okay, I guess I can't
Any
I wasn't doing nothing behind you. Sorry
It's fine. You don't have any balls anyway
Yeah, that's what she said
Can't get me pregnant
I'm trying to get in the car. You fucking asshole
Uh, let's go over here. Let's see what that is
Oh, careful. Oh, can't find it. Can I have a bunny should I go in and try to run over the bunny?
All right, I'm gonna let you do it. Just oh there's nothing right here
Oh, come on. I'll find a bird kill it kill it. Hey kill it. Hey, you know what hammer
Okay, you know what the hammer is building the hammer is just rebuilding. Oh
He likes me
Do I get nothing out of that?
Can I beat it to death with this log this will turn the punch
Oh trash. Oh, yeah, I get to pick up litter. Oh, yeah. Oh, I it's following me now. I think we could kill it
Look, there's a plane
I'm picking the plane
I'm picking the plane. D. You're paying the plane
Oh, he said best feature in the game so far
Can I miss rabbit walk in the fire or is it go?
Bunny come here. Where'd it go?
the boy super real come here
Okay
Nigga, it's right here. No, it's over here. I'm saying not following me no more. Nice over here
Just gets a friend of mine. It's right here
Dude nothing there. It's right here. I'm did nothing there on my screen big fella. I don't know what you want from me
Frinic it's okay. We're gonna get you the best doctors. That's what they said
They're like to me. Yep fire. Do you think if we get the can't fire leave it going it'll
Burn down the woods. Yeah, we could try
I mean have we been putting out any other ones?
Nope
Yeah, then it'll be fine
It's a good thing. We're heading towards a fire watch so
Oh, I wouldn't look at the map
Open your map and
Don't worry. I
Look at the objectives list. Give me a you are a game developers worst nightmare
Where's that bro? They have a list a lit telling you what to do and you're like, what am I trying to supposed to do
There's a list there's a trump down list
Of what you're supposed to do if you could get long tried
You get by a burner and you're vehicle to recharge it. Okay. Can I use droned? Hold on come on here
Come on come on come down. Yes. Yes. I can't go in it now. Yes
It doesn't work. Fuck
I forget what I just said
Now how how to fuck do we how do we how do we how do we charge this ship?
How do we motor info? Well according to my calculations
It's got to be in the front
Hate dumbass. There's nothing different
Oh, that's the fiber tour. Okay
There we go, not the motor and battery. It's in the bio engine bio burner. Yeah
Stop some fiber and they need
I'm gonna put some trash in here to get some more tickets
Actually want to go to sleep since it's nighttime where you want to start driving since it's nighttime. We drive since it's nighttime
All right. Do you want to drive?
I'm the woman. I can't drive
Yeah, yeah, right now. Let me hold your legs
You can hold my third leg hold on there's berries
We're gonna need food because you're dumbass killed yourself in the fire
Now I got full help and I think once I rest again my help back
Okay
Okay, fire
We can always had a bridge
Oh broken bridge good thing that popped up. I was about to drive right over that bitch
I walk up to the campfire thing
but
dipshit
You dumb motherfucker. Okay, open learn it
I've been opening the door for you this whole time and you're like, oh this time. I'll open the door
Yeah
I thought I took them to bed. That's how I was standing around slowly
Fresh new shut up white man. Okay. No fire goes up next day. I guess
Unless you didn't like that people phrases. I didn't like that one. I didn't either
You better calm down there pal
Why are you rehearsing this time? I can't think of any other white people phrases. I was like get a load of this guy dude
You say dude everyone says dude with the fuck
Like get a load of this guy you're getting on my nerves pal
That's a bullshit
Hey buddy knock it off
And that's bullshit
What are you doing
Fuck, what are we doing? It's your face. I was gonna say your sister base. This is actually nice
Your face
Three key items to unlock the step bro. I'm stuck
Step bro. I'm stuck. I went up for yo
I found the you I found the oops stick
I found the password databank. I found the banana
Find teetos
We're kind of sitting down on my door
You hear that beeping sound yeah, he just heard that
No, you know that sounds like that was in my head no
Ross
I
Is that beeping that sound like the Ross science room?
Do it do it do it do it do hey when it's gonna be on sale man
It's gonna be on sale. I don't know
Look up the rock. I did I hit you in the head with a camera
Okay, no, I'm not wasting my rock
Rocko it's rocko of no it's a rocko leave me alone
Of course
I'm gonna go through the rocko. I'm grabbing all the rocko
Leave rocko the load
90 fuck now
That's what you get. I've collected all 500 pine cones
Either her to get needed 90 of them. Did you see that? 90 rock?
Nah, do you remember that guy all of youtuber? He's uh, my name is Soski Boeski
Oh, shit wait, no, I gotta find the fucking oh, what's his name?
buying bitch
So scade Boeski
Yeah, this guy
Oh
Give me a beep head so going on for sure
Yeah
All right, you watch this later
So I don't sound I sound less crazy everyone on youtube knows what i'm talking about
pros D
My name is Soski Boeski
The main villain he's like, how'd you get so strong? He's like, oh, I found all 900 pine cones
Making a lot of collectibles and games
Uh, anyway slow your harvest crops your garden away download gardening
Or food products. Sorry. So woman. Do you want a garden or do you want to cook cook? Obviously
Do you want weeder meth
both
So we can either grow weed or cook meth which one do you want to do? Oh grow weed, obviously
All right to make it motherfucker
Find and use ginger to restore health. I'll know find some ginger consume some ginger
And don't what did you just do? What did you just do down the stereo?
Come here. Look. Look at me. Look at me. She'll be
I
All right, what should we go down the stairs come down? Okay, what should we go down to say?
Oh my god, that's amazing
Most of the game ever yeah, so it's amazing dude
The heck
We're wrecking more you're going on an adventure. Oh jeez, Rick
That I didn't even see you properly. It's a no, right. You're going to play nominate
We're gonna play no game now
Okay, I push you off
It's not killer ourselves in case we want to come back
Oh, I found ginger
All right, so that's ginger
What a figure
Ginger
You didn't know what that's what ginger plant looks like looks like grass on time. It's a root
No, it's a root, but I didn't know what the plant looked like the the top part
It's the reddish
I'm talking. I never seen one before
Oh, bro. I know what the ginger root looks like dude. Who doesn't
I have no idea what ginger looks like line. Turn over gun
All right, unlock water
What gardening? Yeah, okay. Why right?
So, um, I want you to research the axe because I want you to play them in a game
Ah
You know what they're not bad when to get each of them
They're not bad before you get used to them. They're super fucking easy. Oh, there I'm done
That didn't take long, didn't you? Yeah, I just miss one
Yeah, you struggle on the push up mini game and gpo for hockey
It's not a push up
Or whatever the meditation it's push up some slayers, but it's the same like bar. That's why I was never a slayer, dude
I
Don't have different demons. You're right. That's the reason
Yeah
So like demons more entire personality around maybe demons because you didn't want to do push-ups
I'm stuck
You piece of shit. You didn't do the axe
I did do the axe. Maybe he didn't unlock for you
Awesome stuff
I'm stuck
All right, menu unstuck
Okay, so that's the thing but yeah here. I'll show you the video. I gotta stop it. No, because I know I have to get
It's really no such show me your fucking screen dipshit. Oh, I don't believe you
Okay, oh and you didn't get gardening. Okay
Because I got gardening. Okay
I'm gonna have to use our resources to make two axes. That's fine. It's stupid
Maybe resources don't share
I doubt it. All right, we can save here if you want
You play a gnome game. Yeah, get in here and snuggle up
All right, I click save and quit
All right, they even quit
We're playing like a gnome game now. I said it makes sense. We'll see what I can make sense. I get that
I
I could just be asking Google this question. Not me. Why would care? No, no, no, no, no, I'm gonna watch this video
Okay, muting this card muting me good
Can't turn you up though because
No, I'm keeping that part in okay, okay turn your volume to get me better
Oh
Well, I'm like goodness
Look at the hands. I'm holding you
I'm holding your balls. I'm gonna turn you up in the settings. That's why I said that's what I was saying put your
me up
Are you sure you can hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you. You said turn me up. Okay. All right. Let's go in this thing mouth. Wait, why I'm grabbing on there
All right, go back out there. Go back out there. Turn me all the way up and go back out there. Okay
Open your mouth
You know Kenya
52 blood clot pussy wagon chicken nugget
Oh
Reloading the game. Oh, what's going on?
What what what?
Yo
Hey
Plop
No team backup some oh
Oh
You get some I just thought you exploded
I brought my legs to keep bouncing up and down
I
52 blood clot pussy wagon chicken nugget. Oh, wait, can I get on your head? Can I get your head
Like all of me the call me get your heads off
Thank you catch
I can't stand up stand up stand up
Stand up
Okay, maybe crouch or here
Get on my head and then try and grab the door
I got the door you grab the handle
Okay, okay
All right
Why is it latched on both sides is it a like a draw? I don't think we're supposed to go in there fam
I
Whoa mushroom
Was this like a king?
I'm gonna stretch you
It's like that one statue in
Uh human fall flat and we would touch his cock
Oh, this is the flight. I'm real lending
No, let's go break into this white man's house. Thank you finally
We're role-playing is black people
No
We're gonna break in vandalize his stuff and and steal a steal from him
Why are we gonna run back why didn't we not just walk up the state like we're supposed to normal like to go into the back
Plus you're black, you know, you always got to be stealthy with these things
You know how to steal
No, I don't know stolen before
Poof, why are you?
So you think they can you think they can hear us on the mic
Who?
There
Oh, bitch fuck you
Oh, he's got a sleep
Hey shut the fuck up maybe
And I'm trying to do his attention
Where'd you go?
Come here
You got my hands
Got my hands
Help me up, dude
I can't dog
Push you like
Yeah, I can't
Let's go let's go vandalize your shit. All right, bet
Oh my goodness
I broke my legs, dude
You fucking blew up. Holy shit. You broke broke your legs. Yeah
What no, you're like right here
Where am I walking on?
You have new legs. Oh, whoa. Oh, I thought I was gonna do it. I saw how my goodness
pilot
Oh, oh shit. I can't climb up
Oh my gosh, dude. I heard that
I thought it was the dude coming in
Oh, there's clambering. Okay
Oh
Yes
Who's based
Oh, oh relaxed from what you doing? I didn't even get up there
I
Didn't even get that
Faaah, yo, how did he not tear that? I don't know if I can't aim it
I didn't know the aim it
I don't know maybe just a fucking game. Oh, yeah, he's here. Is it?
Why did I drop the gun?
Put me down. Fucking old cracker. Put me down. Put me down
Very
I can see your dentures on the table. Put me down. You fucking shoot him
Shoot it. It was so crap. You ripped my arms off. Okay, I shoot him. I got the gun
Uh
Where is he taking me?
See, he's gonna put me down his pants and shit on me
You good fam? Why didn't you, why didn't you save me?
How could I have saved you tell me tell talk to me young Midoriya. How could I save you?
He did it. It's my cock.
Oh, he like you make a little path for us
Did he? Did he? I mean no
Shut up. There's a little path here. Is this a gun too?
Oh my goodness. You ripped my arms off
What happened? You ripped my arms off. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Stay holding on. Stay holding on
Hold on
And then they eat you
No, no, no
All right, let's fucking I don't even get in there
You know
Come on also can grab you guys pull you up. Yeah, see yeah, well, I couldn't reach you
It's not swinging
Yeah, wait hold up. Wait a minute something right
You got a dog house. No dog though. Maybe
We'll go run into a dog watch
Hey, I'm not oh I am
You're not saying you see it
Oh, I see the same as the barn. Yeah
Run like oh she walk all day around here and there's no way to get back on the other side
What
Oh
It was just right there. Where's the gun? Where's the gun? Pussy wagon
He'd be deep right help help me help me aim the gun at him somehow
Wait a second can I stand on the gun?
Let go let go let go
And then can I can I fly with this no
Dang that'd be so cool. Please rest in one try that before
Yeah, I can't help you end up big fella. Yeah
He's got our roof
Where'd you go? I went in the mouse the mouse hole
Hey, yo
Hey, oh
Oh my goodness
Are you good sir?
Yeah
Look at me look at me. Oh
There's a time limit. Oh you're in the robot. Help me. Help me
, bro
Clutch stop dude. Good job. Good site
Alright, yeah, I'm getting off nate, you don't want to do one more?
That's what we're doing.