this is the menu again, the answer to the outcome.
I think you need to do the tutorial as well.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe.
I mean, I could also use brothers.
What the hell?
Yeah, I don't see why you wouldn't be able to.
Wait, can you use Hentai?
Bro.
Can you do it?
Does it let you do it?
Why would it let me do it?
Try it.
Oh my God, it did.
Really?
I was using your world.
We're using your car.
Holy shit.
You're so good.
Why did they work?
I'm glad I told you to do it.
Check it.
We're using your fucking car.
Where'd I go back?
Go back to work.
You're talking about anything?
I did go back.
Okay.
No, my fault.
It didn't cancel.
Thank God.
You're still using Hentai?
Mm-hmm.
I think it's all scammy like that, bro.
It's the most important thing right now.
Is that what you make your license plate Hentai?
I'm everything my diet right now.
You're making your character?
Mm-hmm.
And I made mine already.
Dude, it looks fucking ugly as hell.
I believe it.
If they're based off you, then you're definitely.
I mean, you can't change as a default.
Guys, make yourself a woman.
No, I should.
I mean, that way you can have sex in the camper bin.
He's a bitch.
I want to see what the sex scene is like in the kitchen.
He's a bitch sussi baka.
Also, I'm recording.
You know, I'm kitchen.
Oh, this is right now.
Oh, you heard all that?
Yeah.
I want to fuck you like an animal, dude.
Shit.
[LAUGHTER]
This is getting all over the internet.
No, homo.
What do you mean?
Wow, you like shell silver-stein dude.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't even know who that is.
It's the first celebrity name that came to my mind.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I'd have you gasping for air.
Like, what's his name?
Alo Yvettean.
No.
[LAUGHTER]
No, like, what's the fucking black guy?
Yeah, Nate.
This is from the black guy.
Like, I can't breathe.
Like, whoa.
[LAUGHTER]
What's it saying?
I ain't telling you that.
Mark Henry, no.
No.
What?
You said, boy, Henry.
That was his name.
Like, what's his name?
[INAUDIBLE]
Yeah, you've been hit.
It's a dude who plays Minecraft Dream, one of their names.
I don't know.
Why the fuck would I know their names?
You think I'm a fucking 12-year-old?
[LAUGHTER]
Why the fuck would I know the name of one of Dream's friends?
Why do you know the names of one of Dream's friends?
[LAUGHTER]
That was a dream.
What the fuck?
I just put it on before I go to bed sometimes.
Also--
I'm ignoring you, but you get to sleep.
Yeah.
She also-- I'm in.
I'm driving around right now, but they're talking.
So I'm going to be quiet.
I'm also turning it up.
Am I done at the tutorial?
Oh, I am done at the tutorial.
Are you done at the tutorial?
I'm driving around.
All right, open your menu, click multiplayer,
and it says show multiplayer code.
You need to come to the intro for it before I be able to--
I will be asking you to.
Hey, you can't say that.
Why not?
I'm black.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
[LAUGHTER]
Nah, actually, I don't want that disability labeled on me.
Nah, I want to--
[LAUGHTER]
Whappower!
OK, yep.
You didn't cancel.
That's where--
Just--
Yeah, and cancel me.
I'm invincible.
So that guy from the TV show who's dead
plowed him through a tree.
Told dad plowed him through a tree, wow.
He's dead good.
Oh, what is-- Oh, put save as a campfire.
Like, who saved yourself at a campfire?
Like, I'm just going to go to the campfire and strike it up,
but just come back here every time I need to go somewhere else.
Dark Souls.
Yeah, I was saying why.
Why is that a thing?
Is this because Dark Souls invented it and just everyone
just copied Dark Souls?
Probably.
Yeah, probably.
[LAUGHTER]
OK, I can.
Did you try to jump off the cliff?
Yeah, there was a wall there.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh.
Shit, game it's done.
If I want to kill myself, I should be allowed to do it.
Right?
I'm literally--
who's who knows?
He's the black guy who killed me.
I'm not telling you.
What's his name?
No.
I'm so close to him.
Say please.
Give me the first letter of his name.
Please say please.
OK, please tell me the first letter of his name.
Echo boy.
It's G.
George Floyd.
[LAUGHTER]
Look that guy.
Anyway, as I'm plowing you in our RV
because you picked a woman, I'm going
to make you gasp for air like George Floyd.
Type shit.
You made yourself a woman, right?
Nope.
[LAUGHTER]
No, I'm gay.
Could you imagine?
You just like, you're married to your wife like 18 years.
And one day you're like, yeah, I decided
that I did a fine woman.
You're gay male.
I'm gay.
[LAUGHTER]
Craft one rent.
I'm to open.
For all the two people watching this on YouTube, gay people.
[LAUGHTER]
Yo.
What are you doing?
He's giving me work to edit and rent.
Quit it.
I know I am.
[LAUGHTER]
Open the mirror.
I just--
The AI cuts out the entire video except for this part based on--
Amazing.
Babe, try to fire a lookout.
Graphic.
Come on.
I already know what I'm doing.
I got a lot.
This is Jorial.
Where's the dirt road at?
Is it right here?
Look.
What the fuck are--
Hmm.
This barrier.
Let her fuck her, dude.
Let me see if I can make a ramso.
I'll flip my sister.
Where am I going to make the rent chat?
I don't know where to go.
To the back of the vent.
How the fuck are you selling back?
[LAUGHTER]
You find the metal behind your van,
and then you go to the back of the van,
just like Rosa Parks went to the back of the bus.
Wait, where did you find the metal at?
All right here.
Oh.
You just craft it in the back of your van.
Why is the pickup so slow?
I don't know, but I thought of something the other day, right?
Yeah, sure you did.
I thought of something.
I didn't see it on Instagram.
I swear I thought of this.
I don't believe you.
Women be lying so much.
They probably just ask Rosa Parks to just move over.
I saw you saw it on Instagram.
I know you guys are saying that.
I thought about this the other day.
No.
Her husband also has a car.
I also thought about this the other day.
Did you know Japan's trip was steps into energy?
Come in, Judas.
What did you laugh at?
I'll put this in storage.
You know what's hilarious?
No, I don't know.
I saw that shit on like an article like three or four years ago that Japan was starting
to implement that like thing into their crosswalks or whatever.
And all of a sudden everyone in Instagram was just like, hey guys, you know this?
I'm like, oh, I thought everyone knew this already.
You what?
I thought that Japan was putting like pressure plates underneath some of their sidewalks
to generate energy because so many people walk down in Shibuya.
Oh.
Because that was like a pretty big talking point four years ago when they were first
implementing it.
Like I, my dad knew about that and my dad doesn't like know shit about anywhere outside
of America and he knew that.
It was a pretty big talking point for a while.
I could go into fire.
I'm going to fire.
All of a sudden it's why would you walk over.
I do this to fire.
It hurts.
Oh, I'm supposed to leave the van and start walking down the path.
Why didn't you?
Ah, that's why I need to scratch the wrench.
I don't know how to have anything to do walking down the path.
Look, you craft the wrench so you can open the vent, the open the...
You're dumb.
I'm not paying attention.
I'm not playing the game.
Yeah, I wasn't paying attention either.
And I thought you craft the wrench so you can open the fence and drive your car out.
Oh, you're supposed to have the car out?
I was walking and go back and go.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
What?
You can do multiplayer.
Okay.
It's a couple of days.
Oh my gosh.
Hurry up.
I'm going to tell you to hurry up and I'm going to take in the longest.
Yeah, also I already told the name of the game when you told me to hurry up.
Yeah.
I told you before that you need to hurry up.
Wiggah?
I don't say the N word.
I say Wiggah.
That's how it...
I would never say the N word.
Bro, how did you crash?
There was nothing in front of you.
Brother.
Why are you blaming the character like you're not the one driving?
Because he's a woman.
So you did make yourself a woman?
I did.
Yeah, I'm not getting anywhere.
He's still gay.
I literally named Instagram gay.
Therefore, he's gay.
No.
You're like boys.
Shut up.
You know it.
Well, I named you Nick.
You're like...
What is that?
Ah!
Oh my goodness.
That's shut up.
What should I make your name?
Because that's not funny.
Nothing you do is as funny.
Bonne, blood clot.
Pursue, wagon.
Chick, ask too many.
Good.
Okay, ask to do 47, bomb, blood clot.
Pursue, wagon.
There you go.
I'm not going to believe it.
What is it?
Send it.
It's not your hand tie.
What?
I'm not going to believe it.
What is it?
Send it.
You're not your hand tie.
What?
I said it to your discord.
That's the code.
I don't get it.
It's supposed to be hand tie, but they change it to that.
That looks nothing like hand tie.
I know it was supposed to be hand tie.
That's what I thought.
But I think the game would just stay the bad word there and give me this random ass code.
No, that's your joint.
That's going to be different every time.
It's the join code.
Yeah, then your license plate is hand tie.
It'll go check.
Oh, it is.
Oh, my God.
Actually,
you're not joined, my guy.
I'm not going to be a fan of the game.
I'm going to be a fan of the game.
I'm a fan of the game.
If it is started, we'll just play the gaming game
whenever we get the chance.
[
]
Everything cloth is a curtain.
If you want to say something and make it
and say something cloth,
then you're good.
Is it cloth or cloth?
Like cloth.
Why cloth?
What does cloth mean?
Back in the day,
slave with the females
used to have their site cut
instead of using headphones,
which they didn't have to use cloth.
You are saying cloth.
You can't pronounce it.
Thank you.
Th at the end.
Do you know how to spell?
Do you know what a cloth is?
No.
How do you spell cloth?
You asked me Google or Google?
spell blood clot. BLR D. C. L. A. T. I with D L A. A. T. So then what was the
story of the reasoning behind it?
I'm fucking female cycle thing tampon. They wiped their pussy with a clot?
No, they use it as a source to stop the bleeding. They're white. I don't know if they're fucking white.
Put it.
What's a clot? What is it? What's a clot? What the hell is a C. L. O. T. What is that?
C. L. O. T. H. No, you spelled it as C. L. O. T. You did not use an H.
No, it's C. L. A. T. C. L. A. T. What is that?
This is a cuss word blood clot pussy clot. It had a mean it.
No, it doesn't. It isn't for me. It's just a cuss word.
I'll tell you what shit means. What the fuck does clot mean?
Oh, it don't have no mean, honey.
Just like everything the black people do has no meaning.
I already have to download the fucking no mean.
I mean, there's no more. It is my second.
It makes sense. Pussy wagon makes sense. I get that.
He claimed that it is the exit in Google. This question, not me.
Why would I ask the resident to make the token black guy?
He's at the oldest top.
Pussy wagon. See, I understand.
This is the name I'm looking for.
I understand the meaning behind pussy wagon.
It's a wagon to pussy right there. That man's got game.
Oh, no. Pussy.
Pussy.
Noodity.
Whoa.
Sensored. Oh, the sensor to disabled. Is there a, is there an uncensored version?
No, I have to go on ajinnemy.org to see the uncensored version.
What are you looking for? The big fella.
Oh, hey, whoa.
Oh, no, just as newlyons. Oh, it's zero.
Goodness. The camera angle is so strange.
Sometimes. Oh, are you in?
I'm in this tutorial. Yeah.
Oh, I thought we weren't playing this.
Sorry, niggas. I'm playing this tutorial.
Oh, are you all made me?
Well, I thought we were.
All right. I guess we're playing this tutorial, then.
No, I joined the game. I already exit.
Host the game.
Doctor.
Join me.
What the foot?
Ah, ah, stand up.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Yeah, it's weird, didn't it?
Sensitivity.
Point.
Nine.
Okay, that's fine.
All right, me, menu.
Host game.
Start hosting.
All right, I'm hosting game.
Stand up.
There we go.
All right. How do I?
Pussy wagon.
Noodie.
Oh, that's what you were talking about.
The say book.
Are you streaming now, still?
Yeah.
Oh.
Pussy wagon.
Were you streaming my whole blood clot on keeping?
Yeah, but.
Shit.
They see how stupid the eye was.
Stiffy shit.
I was.
I'm not stupid.
It was a genuine question.
I don't know.
Why did the plot come from?
We were so passionate about it.
Yeah, where the fuck does the plot come from?
Control shifts.
It comes from your mother.
No.
She is a woman.
Invite the game.
There we go.
I'd hope.
I'm not a woman.
It don't feel good going online and inviting the game, right?
Well, I forgot I was offline because playing porn games.
Dude, I'm streaming.
You're not there.
You don't care.
No one knows who you are.
No one's going to watch this video.
Okay.
Mute in this card.
Mute in this key.
I'm going to go fuck you.
Can you hear me?
Good.
Yeah.
I can hear you.
All right.
Yeah.
Can I turn you up though?
Because you got a nice little mouth on you.
Shit.
Mm.
Maybe cut that part out of the video.
No.
I'm keeping that part in.
Okay.
Turn your volume to get in me better.
Well, I'm like goodness.
Look at the hands.
I'm holding it.
Why do you do this like that?
I'm holding your bows.
I'm going to turn you up in the settings.
That's why I said that's what I was saying.
Put your,
turn me up.
Are you sure you can hear me?
Yeah.
I hear you.
Is it.
Turn me up.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Let's go in this thing mouth.
Why?
I'm grabbing a bond.
Well, go back out there.
Go back out there.
Turn me all the way up and go back out there real quick.
Ah.
Fuck.
No, I said what I wanted.
No.
Shit.
Open your mouth.
You can't.
Ah.
Can you hear me?
You hear me?
You know I can, yeah.
52 blood clots.
Pussy wagon.
Chicken.
No, get.
Oh, reloading the game.
Oh, what's going on?
What?
Yo.
Hey.
Blop.
No team backup.
Some.
Oh.
Me mama.
You got some?
I thought you exploded.
I brought my legs.
Can you keep bouncing me up and down?
Me mama.
52 blood clots.
Pussy wagon.
Chicken.
No, get.
Wait, can I get in your head?
Can I get in your head?
Stop.
Like, hold me.
The goal of me.
Get your heads off me.
Like a couch.
couch.
Okay.
I can't stand up, stand up, stand up.
Ah, shit.
All right, stand up.
Okay, wait, wait, maybe crouch or here.
Get on my head and then try and grab the door.
I got the door.
You got the handle?
If I were to reach it.
Okay.
All right.
Well, I said latched on both sides.
Is it like a draw?
Like, is it like?
I don't think we're posted going there, fam.
Like whatever.
Oh, mushroom.
Was this like a key?
Look at this statue.
It's like that one statue in,
uh, human fall flat that we would touch his cock.
Oh, no.
This is the, this is like a real ending.
No, I'll go break into this white man's house.
Thank you.
Finally.
We're role-playing is black people.
No.
We're going to break in Vanuysa stuff and steal a steal from him.
Why are we going on back?
Why didn't we not just walk up the state like we were supposed to.
I'm like to go into the back.
Plus you're black.
You know, you always got to be stealthy with these things.
You know how to steal.
No, I don't know.
I've stolen before.
Poof.
Why are you?
So?
Do you think they can, do you think they can hear us on the mic?
Poof.
Fucking dude.
I don't know.
Gosh.
Fucking.
No.
There.
Oh, wait for you.
For you.
I can't.
I'll be in the sleep.
Hey, shut the fuck up, maybe.
And I'm trying to do his attention.
Where'd you go?
Oh.
Come here.
You got my hands?
Got my hands.
Put me up, dude.
I can't, dog.
For sea legs.
Yeah, I can't.
Let's go.
Let's go vandalize this shit.
All right, bet.
Oh my goodness.
You're doing it.
I broke my legs, dude.
You fucking blew up.
Holy shit.
You broke broken your legs.
Yeah.
What?
No, you're like right here.
What am I walking on?
You have new legs.
Oh, whoa, whoa.
I thought I was going to do it.
I saw it.
Oh my goodness.
Pilot.
Oh, oh, shit.
I can't climb up.
Oh my gosh.
Dude, I heard that.
I thought it was the dude coming in.
Oh, this clamoring.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Who's based?
Oh, relax.
From what you're doing.
I didn't even get up there.
I didn't even get that.
Yo, how did he not tear that?
I didn't do the aim it.
I don't know.
Maybe he's just a fucking guy.
Oh, yeah.
He is.
He is a.
Bear.
He ripped my arm, though.
Okay. I shoot him.
I got the gun.
Where is he taking me?
See, he's going to put me down his pants and shit on me.
You good fam?
Why didn't you save me?
How could I have saved you?
Tell me.
Talk to me, young Midoriya.
How could I save you?
He did.
It's my God.
Look at this.
Oh, he like you make a little path for us.
Did he?
I mean, no.
Shut up.
There's a little path here.
Is this a gun too?
When I was a hoe?
Why would it be a gun?
Oh, my goodness.
You ripped my arms, this.
Well, what happened?
You ripped my arms off.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Stay holding on.
You hold on.
And then he leads you.
Where are my hands now?
Yum yum yum.
Don't do that.
All right, let's fucking--
I don't even get in there.
I'll swing, say.
Fuck yeah.
Get on.
Come on.
Also, it can grab you guys.
Pull you up.
Yeah, see?
Yeah, well, I'm going to reach you.
It's not swinging.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, hold up.
Wait a minute.
It's up me right.
You got a dog house.
No dog though.
Maybe.
But the dog doing--
We're going to run into a dog watch.
Hey, that's stamina.
Oh, I am.
And that's same.
You see it?
Oh, I see the stamina bar now.
Yeah.
You run like--
Once you walk all the way around here,
there's no way to get back on the other side.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
What?
Oh.
Shut up.
It was just right there.
Where's the gun?
Pussy wagon.
In bitty.
Right.
Help me.
Help me aim the gun at him somehow.
Wait a second.
Can I stand on the gun?
Eh.
Let go.
And then can I fly with this?
No.
Dang, that'd be so cool.
Please trust him.
I'm going to try that before.
I can't help you end it, big fella.
Yeah.
He's got our roof.
Where'd you go?
I went in the mouse.
The mouse hole.
Hey, yo.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, there's a field.
There's a field.
Are you good, sir?
Get him.
It's cool.
I want to use this.
Look at me.
Oh.
There's a time limit.
Oh, you're in the wrong way.
Help me.
Bruh.
Bro, clutch stop, dude.
Good job.
Good shite.
All right.
I'm getting off note.
You don't want to do one more?
That's what we're doing.
Nope.