this is the menu again, I think you need to do the tutorial as well and maybe I mean I could also use brothers what the hell we don't see why you wouldn't be able to wait can you use that I bro okay can you do it doesn't let you do it why would it let me do it try it oh my god it did why did it work why does it work well I told you to do it check it we're using your fucking color let's go back go back you talk about anything you talk about anything oh I didn't go back okay nevermind fall didn't it didn't cancel thank god you still use anti thank you don't scare me like that bro there's the most important thing right now
that we make our place in plate and tie I'm everything my diet now you're making your character mm-hmm I made mine already dude looks fucking ugly as hell I believe it they're based off you then yeah definitely I mean you can't change the default guys look make yourself a woman no I should look you and they way you can have sex in the camper bin he's a bit i want to see what the sex scene is like he's a bit so saucy bakka also it may i'm recording you know i'm kitchen all of this sustenance right now oh yeah you heard all that yeah I just want to fuck you like an animal dude holy shit this is getting all over the internet oh no you mean what do you mean what do you mean like shell silver scene dude I don't even know who that is it's the first celebrity name that came to my mind i don't even know who that is i'd have you gasping for air like uh what's his name hello verthon no
no like uh listed the fucking black guy yeah nay this is from black guy i can't breathe like oh wow
i'm telling you that mark had rick no no what
you said where he's that was his name like what's his name but in the hint yeah you mean it's a dude who plays minecraft for dream one of their names i don't know why the fuck would i know their names you think i'm a fucking 12 year old
why the fuck would i know the name of one of dream's friends why do you know the names of one of dream's friends that was a dream what the fuck i just put it on before i go to bed sometimes also you're not worrying you need to sleep you know she also i'm in i'm driving around right now but they're talking so it'll be quite also turning it up am i done the tutorial oh i am done the tutorial are you doing the tutorial i'm driving around i uh open your menu click multiplayer into this a show multiplayer code you need to comfort the intro for it before i be able to be able to
hey you can't say that why not i'm black oh yeah i forgot i know i actually i don't want that disability labeled on me no thank you
what power what power okay yep you didn't cancel that's where just yeah can't see me i'm i'm invisible so that guy from the tv show who's dead plowed him through a tree so that plowed through a tree wow
oh what is up for save as a fire as a campfire like who saved yourself at a campfire like i'm just gonna go to the campfire and strike it up but just come back here every time i need to go somewhere else dark souls yeah i was saying why you're like why is that a thing is this because dark souls invented it and just everyone just copied dark souls yeah probably yeah probably
okay i can did you try to jump off the cliff yeah there was a wall there yeah if i want to kill myself i should be allowed to do it right i'm literally who's who knows he's the black guy who can't i'm not telling me
what's his name no i'm so close say please give me the first letter of his name please say please okay please tell me the first letter of his name hey good boy this is this gene
George Floyd yeah anyway as i'm plowing you in our RV because you picked a woman i'm going to make you gas for air like George Floyd hey shit you made yourself a woman right no
imagine it's like you're married to your wife like 18 years and one day you're like yeah i decided that i didn't find a woman you're gay male
craft one rent i'm to open for all the two people watching this on youtube gay people yo yo what are you doing you're giving me work to edit and rent quit it
open the mirror i cut out the entire video except for this part based on amazing
babe i tried to fire a lookout graphic come on come on i already know what i'm doing i got a lot where's the dark road at is it right here look what the fuck is this barrier letter fucker need i can make a room for my sister where am i gonna make the rent and i don't know where to go
to the back of the van how the fuck are you selling back you find the metal behind your van and then you go to the back of the van just like rose apart went to the back of the bus wait where did you find the metal that all right here oh you just crafted in the back of your van why is the pickup so slow i don't know but i thought of something the other day right yeah sure you did i thought of something i didn't see it on instagram i swear i thought of this i can't believe you women be lying so much they probably just asked rose apart so just move over i saw you saw that instagram i know you guys are but instagram i'm i'm i thought about this the other day no how's her husband also has a car i also thought about this the other day did you know japan's trip they're both stepping to energy come here judith what did you let me you know what's hilarious no i don't know i saw that shit on like an article like three or four years ago that japan was starting to implement that like thing into their their crosswalks whatever
and all of a sudden everyone instagram's just like hey guys you know this i'm like oh i thought everyone knew this already knew what that japan was putting like pressure plates underneath some of their sidewalks to generate energy because so many people walk down in jibulia oh because that was like a pretty big talking point four years ago when they were first implementing it like i my dad knew about that and my dad doesn't like know shit about anywhere outside of america and he knew that it was a pretty big talking point for a while i could go into fire and i'm going to fire all of a sudden why would you walk over hey dude is divine oh i'm supposed to leave the van and start walking down the path why don't you ah that's why i need to scratch the wrench i don't know how to have anything to walk in on the path nika you craft the wrench so you can open the vent the open the
you're dumb i'm not paying attention i'm just playing the game yeah i wasn't paying attention either i thought you craft the wrench you can open the fence and drive your car out oh you're supposed to have the car out i was walking and go back and go back and go walk
you can do multiplayer okay
to couple of days oh my god hurry up bro i'm doing tell you to hurry up and i'm doing taking the longest yeah also i already told you maybe the game when you told me to hurry up yeah told you before that you need to hurry up wiggle i don't say the end word i say wiggle that's how i would never say the end
bro how did you crash there was nothing in front of you brother why are you blaming the character like you're not the one driving because he's a woman so you did make yourself woman i did yeah i'm not getting anywhere it's okay i literally named instagram gay no therefore he's gay no you're like boys no shut up you're like boys you know it well i named you make your own
oh my goodness please shut up what should i what should i make your name because that's not as funny nothing you do is as funny
bonne blood clot for seawegen check us too many good okay us do 47 bonbon blood clot for seawegen there you go ah time to take a rest one from from school
his name is aloha akbar bomber man nightnate join aloha you're not gonna believe it what is it send it what
i said it here this good that's the code for it i don't i don't get it it's supposed to be hentai but they change it to that that looks nothing like hentai i know it was supposed to be hentai but that's what i thought but i think the game would destroy the bad work there and give me this random ass code no that's your that's the joint that's gonna be different every time it's the join code so yeah then your license plate is hentai ah he didn't go check he's fucking idiot oh it is oh my god it actually is
bro are you gonna join my guy i gotta remake my custom character oh my goodness i'm gonna burn myself into fire see what happens i'm gonna kill myself and see what happens find the guys i won't customize the colors because i took too long last time i fainted i'll say absolutely nothing happened i know i have low health though
why'd you make her black now i don't want to fuck the shit out of you that's a good hey come here come here white boy you got money on you white boy come here come here white boy yeah come here i think yeah you like this you like this yeah you like this tunetang boy oh no wait for me
that's fine i hear you're gonna shower now thank god how does it feel to have your car stolen and that's how you make your man drink and you walk girls open the fucking door open the fucking car you're supposed to see that after you get in the car that has some driving past you bro how do i you can't even get in is there's one person what's going on you can drive but we got to do we should wait all right let's just go yeah what are we supposed to do is there a gas in this do we have to get gas uh probably brother i got it's a fucking car yep shit we should do what the objectives say actually uh craft building hammer use ginger to restore health using i'm not going to find ginger paint oh can we start with those blue the blue bushes yeah we can stop the car so can get out okay too tired to sprint okay i can get the merry bushes yeah well there's wood too tired to sprint it took you so long to get past the tutorial it became night time wow and now we can't run because it's the night time one different there's entering the woods i'm gonna get attacked by a skinwalker a bunch of fireflies so yeah where are you i dig where what is that no kidding i'm eating
hey all right i'm gonna back to the car before we get lost you can see the car marked on the compass on the top of your screen i see it Nate it's so smart there's there's a beacon i can't find the car birds got it we're tired mary's i cannot find the car there's not like there's a big beacon tearing the wire it isn't really not running over i'm not running over hey mary's maybe don't try killing a king now hey mary's hey mary's i dodged it mary's i'm a bad boy trying to get in the caribou's i'm going to skin your balls uh
you do that middle mouse button like i work in yeah you just pick the mountains well mary's i think look at the distance look get out get out you just look just look past look look the mountain
look i'm picking the mountain too look at this oh i'm here over there i'm over here Nate why are we allowed to why are we allowed to ping that far away i'm over here dog get in
bro if that either means we're allowed to walk up there or that's just a crazy ping distance they haven't fixed it oh no i see why we need to make a hammer now
hammer yeah did you're going to chop down the trees with the hammer i mean you can try you're not going to get far though you're eating it
all right i think that we needed to make oh my god nate why are you not doing this i think you know what i think i don't care what you think i just made a hammer baby in the car and go to sleep i want to be able to sprint that's what i think
okay i think i want to be allowed to sprint you're gonna oh we can't close it get into bed shit uh uh right that morning breath i was kicking dog that morning what?
breath i'm morning breath yeah i definitely morning breath i'm not the other kind of morning thing that a guy would have yeah i wonder what that guy would have not a guy i wouldn't know especially not for a black chick on the floor
all right building the rv because i already did this because i thought it was part of the tutorial building the rv yeah raspby oct you mean building the rv christy be nigga
where am i building our fold into here i guess no i'm not supposed to look at the objectives oh burl at least one car sir stupid where are you gonna put the counter because i uh you fuck
hey you wanted me to build so you're gonna put your controller in there why would it not be decided better could we have four hundred or something dumb dumb because i don't roll off in an rv i had a i used to have a thing beside my bed i don't know the heck because it broke but i want another one hamper van i would yeah no because first off wait can i go through you is there hit no there's no hit ticker okay i thought there was hit detection because i have because we have to be on each side of the bed i had to scoot over because it wasn't working okay i thought that i didn't know we could go through each other also you are super short is that just me like i have to look down to see your character do you have to look at this in line no i'm looking at your big guy say right now or am i looking for you down hold on you know look look forward look forward look forward no forward you know those you know those beams where it's like high angle pictures look forward i got it
it no we look like one next month to stick to character bro holy shit you're right holy shit you're right we do with the three six jade jade are we gonna build the thing i don't know we need materials dude we need another wood all right let's go back to where there isn't a cross like a a tree trunk in the way i look absolutely stunning but you know what users race just lads don't worry about them
first off black women are disgusting jesus christ where can i even post this kick
youtube sub youtube i'm a minor you're not going to need to wow this session might be a gta at one time for legal purposes that was a joke
no i'm going to pardon that's not what i did now
just no blueberries blueberries i'm god don't stuff was that changing fiber and ever wood
no i'm making why making sounds for boy what
sounds the character looking sound that car mason oh mason get out the car mason you're hungry i don't get food i'm hungry i put i put the blueberries in the car all right yeah yeah i'm tired how do we get access to it because i'm not right here right here versus storage i still it isn't that goofy then some unsumption and i could some some fiber now now i'm turning the fiber into tickets for some reason it's so flat what you're flat but i forgot you're white so i'm a man i'm man i shouldn't have a have you seen gates started to gates but that's not a good thing gates is fucking gay what did you look at so rabbit i kill it
but uh you hitting the road i'm trying to get more wood
oh you want to drive over there yeah i want to drive over there i saw something cool over there dude over there he's not paying no more way is it paying i saw bridge i want to go over to the bridge all right you drive i'm putting it wait can you drive on to the back oh no just puts me the how did i go here you go in the wrong way that where he came from
why is it in reverse then look at that where it came from let's go over there our car is not built for this it'll be fine i'm figuring out the glitter already just go you just go you're playing this like it's GTA also you're hitting a wall like yeah i know i'm trying to go around it
the collision the collision for the vehicle is kind of weird hey i think our car is dying is that the hp bar for the car or is that the energy bar i think that's the energy bar stop what is that what's that what is that what is this what is this what is this
hmm what technology is from the olden times you know technology
technology you know what who act well we need to take a name use the ticket to buy the axe boy get get out of the fucking oh my bad i didn't know i thought but then what's going to fix this yes there we go yes uh compute up i wanted to get the pickaxe too okay i guess i can't i wouldn't do nothing behind you i'm sorry it's fine you don't have any balls anyway
yeah so she said can't get me pregnant in the good i'm trying to get in the car in fucking asshole uh let's go over here let's see what that is oh can't fall out of the bunny should i go over there we'll try to run over the bunny all right come on let you do just oh there's nothing right here oh come on i'll find a bird kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it kill it the hammer's just rebuilding oh well he likes me do i get out of this i get nothing out of that can i beat it to death with this log this one will turn the punch oh trash oh yeah i get to pick up litter oh yeah oh i it's following me now i think we could kill it better look just a plane
do the plane i'm pinging the plane dig you're pinging the plane oh he said best feature in the game so far is pinging the plane can i made it's rabbit walk into fire where's it go bunny come here where did it go the place is the real come here okay nigga it's right here no it's over here oh so it's not following me no more nice over here
just gets a phrenic looking at us it's right here there's nothing there it's right here i'm there's nothing there on my screen big fella i don't know it's too off from me just get the phrenic it's okay we're gonna get you the best doctors that's what they said they're like to me get fire do you think if we get the can't fire leave it going it'll uh burn down the woods yeah it'll go try
i mean have we been putting out any other ones okay no yeah then it'll be fine it's a good thing we're heading towards a fire watch so oh i wasn't looking at the map open your map and
no where's that where would we do that oh i was supposed to do that
look at the objective list can we get you are the game developers worst nightmare where's that the deep bro they have a list a telling you what to do and you're like how what am i truly supposed to do there's a list there's a trump down list of what you're supposed to do your week is getting long tired you're buying a burner and you're vehicle to recharge it okay can you strand upon on come over here come over here come over here come down yes yes i can't go in it now yes it doesn't work fuck uh i forget what i just said now how how to fuck do we how do we how do we how do we charge this shit how do we motor info well according to my calculations it's got to be in the front hey dumbass there's nothing different my calculations oh that's the fiber tour okay there we go not the motor and batteries in the bio engine bio burner yeah stop them fiber do you need fiber i'm gonna put some trash in here to get some more tickets actually want to go to sleep since it's night time where do you want to start driving since it's night time we drive since it's night time all right do you want to drive nah fum i'm the woman i can't drive that's the princess yeah yeah right now let me hold your leg you can hold my third leg hold on there's berries we're gonna need food because you're dumbass killed yourself in the fire nah i got full health nothing quenciar ester gave my help back uh okay yeah okay fire we can we had a bridge oh broken bridge good thing that popped up i was about to drive right over that bitch i guess it's a hill i probably shouldn't oh um it's a hill yes yes hill i'm very intelligent now oh that's the fire thing you were going to really hope the demo doesn't end when we get to the fire thing i really hope that that's time is it are you not you not having fun no i am but i'm gonna go to sleep yeah it was so you didn't have to play this tonight i'm steeple great now this is is this milady milady you want to mark the truck well yeah we were gonna go to sleep because it's night it's about to walk up to the campfire the but you should be dumb mother okay open donate i've been opening a door for you this whole time and you're like uh this time i'll open the door uh i thought i took them to bed that's how it's standing around slowly fresh you shut up white man okay no fire goes up next day i guess okay unless you didn't like that people phrases i didn't like that one i didn't either you better calm down there pal why do you rehearse in this time i can't think of any other white people phrases it's like get a load of this guy dude you say dude everyone says dude what the fuck like get a load of this guy you're getting on my nerves pal hey buddy that's a bull shit hey buddy knock it off and that's a bull shit but you suck at this what are you doing what are you doing what are you doing probably doing it's your face i was gonna say your sister but your sister is actually nice yeah your face can i jump off it is that bro i'm stuck step bro i'm stuck i went up for yo i found the you i found the ousp stick i found the password databank i found the banana i'm fine teetos what kind of sitting down on my door you hear that beeping sound yeah i've just heard that no you know that sounds like
that was in my head no ras just just just just a science i ras just just a science oh shit
go guys bro does that beeping that sound like the ras science from
dude it do it do it do hey when it's gonna be on sale man
when it's gonna be on sale i don't know look up the rock i did i hit you in the head with a camera okay hipster now i'm not wasting my rock rocko it's rocko of no it's a rocko leave me a load of course i'm gonna hold the rocko i'm grabbing all the rockos leave rocko the load
that's what you get i collected all 500 pine cones either or you get needed 90 of them did you see that 90 rock dude now do you remember that guy old youtuber he's uh my name is sosky boesky
oh wait no i gotta find this i can oh what's his name fine bitch sosky boesky yeah this guy holy shit oh it's hilarious the beep is so going on for sure
there we go i need to find you by now all right you watch this later so i don't sound i sound less crazy everyone on youtube knows what i'm talking about pros d maybe mr sosky boesky now i'm wasn't now extreme do we want uh that's not the video it's just that's the youtuber
i know who it is no yeah yeah yeah so you finally when one of his videos he's the the main villain he's like how did you get so strong he's like oh i found all 900 pine cones making a lot of collectibles and games uh anyway slow your harvest crops your garden to wait download gardening or food products sorry so woman do you want a garden or do you want to cook cook obviously do you want weed or meth okay both so we can either grow weed or cook meth which one do you want to do oh girl weed obviously find and use ginger to restore health hell no find some ginger because zoom is some ginger
no what did you just do what do you just do dandestarian come here look look at me look at me oh she'll be right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right all right watch me go dandestays come down me okay watch me go dandestays go go go go go go
oh my god that's amazing most funny game ever yeah so it's gonna be amazing dude the heck that mountain over there you see that mountain over there yeah check it out dude check it out we're wrecking more you're going on an adventure oh jesus rick it's a lecture
look at that i didn't even see you properly it's a no right you're going to play nominate hundred we're going to play no game now
okay i pushed you off i can't push you off let's not just not kill ourselves in case we want to come back oh i found ginger all right so that's ginger what a figure oh no i want a plant ginger you didn't know that's what ginger plant looks like looks like grass sometimes it's a root no it's a root but i didn't know what the plant looked like the top part it's like a reddish i'm talking i never seen one before i never seen one before oh bro i know what the ginger root looks like dude who doesn't talking out of my ass i have no idea what ginger looks like lion's under the gun all right unlock water yeah okay wow right so um i want you to research the axe because i want you to play the mini game you know it did not bear one to get used to them they're not bad before you get used to them they're super fucking easy uh dare i'm done
that doesn't take long didn't you yeah i just miss one yeah you struggle on the push up mini game and gpo for hockey it's not a push up or whatever the meditation it's push up some slayers but it's the same like part that's why i was never a slayer dude
i don't know you don't have to do it for demons you're right that's the reason yeah it's a like demons more entire personality around maybe in demons because you didn't want to do push-ups um stuff you piece of shit you didn't do the axe i did do the axe maybe you didn't unlove for you oh so i'm stuck it didn't blow shit no you didn't i did i'm stuck all right menu on stuff no okay so that's the thing but yeah here i'll show you the video i gotta stop it not because of your acting is really nice so you're fucking screaming dude shit oh yeah i can do it i should do it right i don't believe you okay oh and you didn't get gardening okay
because i got gardening okay so i may have to use our resources to make two axes that's fucking stupid maybe resources don't say i doubt it all right we can save here if you want you play a gnome game yeah get in here and snuggle up all right i click save and quit all right they even quit we're playing like a gnome game now
again i thought you wanted to go to sleep with the fuck uh sure dude you're right i should just see any i see two eyes bro i already launched the gnome game i don't have a gnome load in my world's it called gnome escape gnome gnome oh burning gnomes burgling gnomes bell
burgling gnomes play tutorial or just no tutorial
holy shit this is demo version of burgling gnomes with limited content only one level limited house variations to five no progression or difficulty scaling crafting limited to equipment only generally limited content you still get the whole first level
yeah crap i don't know this one the wrong though how do i count the the camping game we got the whole first world and it said there only going to be three other ones so we got one fourth of the game as the demo
mm-hmm that's crazy however i need to get 100% of this fucking evolve idol game because i need more helium storage but i can't get it without having more helium how the fuck am i supposed to get more helium hey maybe something else give you helium nothing does i'm hovering helium i must need to get my knowledge up so i can fucking research something that gives me more helium but i don't remember there being something that gives me more helium
i just want to reset i'm right there dude i need
i need 2,800 more helium storage and i'm able to reset what this fucking game will not let me bro this game brother just let it happen no just let it happen no i don't want the hypnosis it looks tired it
and if it is started we'll just play the camping game whenever we get the chance 452 bomb blood clot per se wagon i am Jamaican weed you like a lot bussy clot to weed clot
that's not a lot penis clot everything you go everything clot is occur dude and if you want to say something and Jamaican just say something clot and then you're good mother clap shit clot is it clots or cloth blood clot why clot what does clot mean you know back in the day slave day with females used to have their psycho instead of using cataphones which they didn't have to use cloth so you are saying cloth it's just you can't pronounce it okay thank you yeah t h at the end t h at the end i don't know do you know how to spell it's not a not a spell what i spell do you know what a cloth is no it is a cloth and lighted but the i think it's a cloth
yes and me google art google how about this spell blood clot b l r d ph e l a a t how it b l a a t area okay so then what was the story of the reasoning behind it fucking female phico thing tampon they wiped their pussy with a clot
no they use it as a source to stop bleeding they're like why i don't know if they're fucking white put it
what's a clot what is it what's a clot what the hell is a clot what is that clot h no you spelled it as clot you did not use an h no let's see l a t clot okay c l a t what is that and this is a cuss word blood clot pussy clot or a clot and i had a minute i mean sex means uh no it doesn't it isn't how it means it's a cuss word i'll tell you what she means poop what the fuck does clot mean oh i don't have no me honey just like everything the black people do has no meaning hurry up and download the fucking no meaning i mean there's no no it is my second it makes sense we'll see what i can make sense i get that he claimed it could just be a single girl this question not me why would i want to ask the resident to make the token black guy he's at the oldest top pussy wagon see i understand the meaning behind pussy wagon pussy right there that man's got game nudity whoa censored absolutely oh just censored or disabled is there uh is there an uncensored version no word i have to go on a anime dot uh uh a anime dot org to see the uncensored version what are you looking for the big fella oh hey whoa i know just it just is newly it's oh
anything zero uh hmm goodness the camera angle is so strange something oh are you in i'm in the tutorial yeah oh i thought we weren't playing it so niggas they're not playing the tutorial
uh already oh made me well i thought we were all right i guess we're playing this tutorial then no i joined the game i already exit host the game stuff i joined me stand up oh shit okay yeah it's weird didn't it sensitivity point nine
okay that's fine all right me menu host game start hosting
all right i'm hosting game stand up there we go all right how do i pussy wagon no that's what you were talking about the save work are you streaming now still yeah pussy like were you streaming my whole blood clot argument yeah
they see how stupid y'all are stupid shit i was i'm not stupid it was a genuine question i don't like black com from you were so passionate about it yeah where the fuck this comes from control shift it comes from your mother she is a woman invite the game there i'd hope it don't feel good going online and inviting the game right
well i sure got i was offline because playing porn games yeah dude i'm streaming you're not you don't care no one knows who you are no it's gonna watch this video okay muting this card muting this key shift can you hear me good
that's right yeah yeah yeah can't turn you up though because you got a nice little mouth on you shit
maybe cut that part out of the video no i'm keeping that for i didn't okay okay turn your volume figure it made me better oh oh my goodness look at the hands i'm holding it i'm holding your bows i'm gonna turn you up into the settings that's why i said that's what i was saying put you turn me up are you sure you can hear me yeah i hate you it's a term yeah okay all right let's go in this thing mouth wait why i'm grand bonding go back out there go back out there turn me all the left and go back out there okay no i said i want no no open your mouth do you know can yeah 52 blood blood pussy wagon chicken no get oh reloading the game
oh what's going on what what yo no hey
plop
no team backup semi oh oh oh did you get some i thought you exploded i broke my legs gonna keep bouncing up and down i'm gonna get a little bit more
52 blood blood pussy wagon chicken no get oh wait can i get on your head can i get your head like boom the gummy get your heads off catch catch catch i can stand up stand up stand up
i should be all right stand up oh shit okay maybe crouch or here get on my head and then try and grab the door
try another door you got the handle if you were to reach it okay all right why is it latched on both sides is it like a trombone like i don't think we're posted going there fam oh mushroom was this nigga king who is statue it's like that one statue in uh human fall flat we would touch his cock no just do is this like a real ending
no i let's go break into this white man's house thank you finally we're we're role-playing is black people no we're gonna break in vandalize the stuff and and steal a steal from him why are we going on back why didn't we not just walk up the state like we're supposed to normally like to go into the back
plus you're black you know you always got to be stilting with these things you know how to steal no i don't know it's stolen before
who are you so do you think you think they can hear us in the mic who the fucking dude oh gosh oh wait for you
oh you got a sleep hey shut the fuck up maybe and i'm trying to do his attention where'd you go oh come here you got my hands got my hands
hook me up dude i can't dog for sea legs yeah i can't let's go let's go vandalize this shit all right bet oh my goodness i broke my legs dude
you're fucking blew up holy shit you broke broke your legs okay yeah what no you're like right here what am i walking on you have new legs oh whoa i thought i was gonna do it i saw oh my goodness oh pilot oh oh shit i can't climb up
oh my gosh dude i heard that i thought it was the dude coming in oh there's clambering okay oh yes who's based
yo oh relax from what you doing how'd you even get up there i didn't even get that
yo how did he not tear that i don't know if i can't aim it or do the aim it i don't know maybe just the fucking thing oh yeah he is he is it oh put me down fucking old cracker put me down put me down there
i can see your dentures on the table put me down shoot me shoot
you ripped my arms up okay i shoot him i don't got the gun where is he taking me see he's gonna put me down his pants and shit on me
you good from why didn't you save me how could i have saved you tell me tell talk to me young menoria how could i save you oh he'll like you make a little path for us
did he did he i mean no shut up there's a little path here is it gone too when i was a hoe this why would it be gone oh my goodness you ripped my arms this well what happened you ripped my arms up oh hold on hold on hold on stay holding on oh i'm not holding on
hold on yeah go go go go oh what the fuck and then they eat you oh where are my hands now yum yum yum dog dude that was so good i don't even get in there
oh i swing same fuck yeah get on get on get on come on also it can grab you guys pull you up yeah see
yeah well i'm gonna reach you start swinging okay yes wait hold up wait a minute something you're right
you got a dog house no dog though maybe we're gonna run into a dog watch hey i'm not oh i am and i'm saying you see it oh i see the same to burn up yeah once you walk all they're around here and there's no way to get back on the other side what
oh shot shot shot it was just right there where's the gun where's the gun pussy wagon
you're bitty right help help me help me aim the gun at him somehow
wait a second can i stand on the gun let go let go let go
and then can i can i fly with this no dang that'd be so cool please rest if i want to try that before
yeah i can't help you end up big color yeah he's got our roof
where'd you go i went in the mouse the mouse hole hey yo hey yo oh my goodness are you good sir hey
go yeah yeah look at me look at me oh there's a time limit oh you're in the robot help me help me
bro clutch stop dude good job good shot all right yeah i'm getting off note you don't want to do one more that what we're doing no